eglobalcentral.eu 2016-11-24

# Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that eGlobal Central collects, and the ways in which eGlobal Central uses that personal information. 

**Personal information collection**

eGlobal Central may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

\- information about your use of this website (including to process the order and to deliver the goods ordered);

\- information that you provide for the purpose of registering for the website (including customer’s full name, physical address, email address);

\- information about transactions carried out over this website (including Credit Card payments unless using the PayPal gateway); and

\- information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services (including tailored product, promotion and terms and conditions updates);

\- information about the data during the use of internet at our server (including host name of the accessing computer, IP address and the time of the server request)

**Using personal information**

eGlobal Central may use your personal information to

\- administer this website;

\- personalise the website for you;

\- enable your access to and use of the website services;

\- display information about you on the website;

\- deliver products that you purchase;

\- supply to you services and products that you purchase;

\- send you statements and invoices;

\- collect payments from you; and

\- send you marketing communications.

**Securing your data**

eGlobal Central will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

eGlobal Central will store all the personal information you provide on its secure servers. Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this website will be protected by encryption technology.

**Updating this statement**

eGlobal Central may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes. 

**Contact information**

https://eglobalcentral.eu

Privacy Policy Supervisor

27/F., E - Trade Plaza,

24 Lee Chung Street,

Chai Wan,

Hong Kong

e-mail: support@eglobalcentral.eu

**To Unsubscribe**

To close an account, please visit our online support centre and submit a ticket. Your user account will be closed and all information removed from our server within 48 hours.

To opt-out from our newsletter subscription, please follow the instructions found at the bottom of the newsletter.

To opt-out from our advertising or promotion inforomation, you can unsubscribe [here](http://www.eglobalcentral.eu/unsubscribe.php).
